export const PROBLEMS = {
    easyMath: {
        question1: {
            question: "What's 7 + 7?",
            choice1: "8",
            choice2: "0",
            choice3: "14",
            choice4: "12",
            correctAns: "14"
        }, 
        question2: {
            question: "What's 3 + 2?",
            choice1: "7",
            choice2: "3",
            choice3: "2",
            choice4: "5",
            correctAns: "5"
        }, 
        question3: {
            question: "What's 9 - 3?",
            choice1: "7",
            choice2: "2",
            choice3: "6",
            choice4: "11",
            correctAns: "6"
        }, 
        question4: {
            question: "What's 5 x 5?",
            choice1: "15",
            choice2: "45",
            choice3: "25",
            choice4: "35",
            correctAns: "25"
        }, 
        question5: {
            question: "What's 30 ÷ 3?",
            choice1: "12",
            choice2: "8",
            choice3: "10",
            choice4: "9",
            correctAns: "10"
        }, 
        question6: {
            question: "What's 7 + 9 - 4?",
            choice1: "10",
            choice2: "12",
            choice3: "11",
            choice4: "9",
            correctAns: "12"
        }, 
        question7: {
            question: "What's 9 + 4 x 2?",
            choice1: "18",
            choice2: "26",
            choice3: "17",
            choice4: "21",
            correctAns: "17"
        }, 
    },

    hardMath: {
        question1: {
            question: "What's 27 x 4?",
            choice1: "104",
            choice2: "108",
            choice3: "96",
            choice4: "112",
            correctAns: "108"
        }, 
        question2: {
            question: "What's 256 ÷ 16?",
            choice1: "14",
            choice2: "16",
            choice3: "15",
            choice4: "12",
            correctAns: "16"
        }, 
        question3: {
            question: "What's √49 x 12?",
            choice1: "94",
            choice2: "76",
            choice3: "84",
            choice4: "62",
            correctAns: "84"
        }, 
        question4: {
            question: "What's √(100 ÷ 4)?",
            choice1: "25",
            choice2: "5",
            choice3: "10",
            choice4: "4",
            correctAns: "5"
        }, 
        question5: {
            question: "What's 8 x 3 x 6?",
            choice1: "166",
            choice2: "122",
            choice3: "144",
            choice4: "188",
            correctAns: "144"
        }, 
    },
}